Afsaneh Sadeghnia

+31 (0) 615357770

Email: x.sadeghnia@gmail.com

Skype: x.sadeghnia

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/afsaneh-sadeghnia-1b32b5108 May 13, 2018 Page 1

IN SUMMARY

As a casual makeup artist and enthusiast, I have always been developing my skills and keeping them up-to-date and fresh through various methods like watching YouTube or Instagram bloggers, working in a professional salon as an assistant, doing hair styling among my friends, etc. I've studied IT Engineering with expertise in Web Engineering field and I've had many manager and specialist rolls in my career but I have always been a casual makeup assistant to my mother which is a professional makeup artist in Tehran, Iran. So, I have the passion from my childhood and from my mother. I want to make this my main profession for the coming years and I've found it a lot more serious and professional here since my move to Amsterdam with my family. I'm a hard worker, positive and exact person who has a strong personality and I'm totally ready to take any action needed for me to go through the makeup profession from being a junior and assistant to be a real first class makeup artist.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Makeup: Hair styling, Hair coloring, Hair highlighting and ombré, Hair coloring using foil
 and cap, Balayage and tip coloring, Root coloring, Hair bleaching, Facial makeup, Bridal
 makeup
- Management: Timetable management, Quality assurance, Accounting and financial auditing, Course management, Syllabus writing, Resource management, Strategy planning, Instructor screening and interviews, Customer relation management,
- Software Engineering: Web development, SEO, Java and PHP programming languages, Web Commerce, Social networks, etc

WORK PERMIT

I have full access to Netherlands' labor market based on my resident permit's decision. I've moved with my husband to Amsterdam who is working for TomTom as a Senior Software Engineer and he is a knowledge migrant.

EMPLOYMENT EXPERIENCES

Bahar Makeup Salon

Tehran, Iran

August 2005 - June 2015

Makeup Assistant

• Hair coloring, Hair highlighting and ombré, Hair bleaching, Balayage and tip coloring, Facial makeup, Financial accounting, Advertisement in social networks, etc

Afsaneh Sadeghnia

+31 (0) 615357770

Email: x.sadeghnia@gmail.com

Skype: x.sadeghnia

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/afsaneh-sadeghnia-1b32b5108 May 13, 2018 Page 2

Tehran Institute of Technology, Vanak Delegacy

Tehran, Iran

June 2015 - February 2017

Director of Web and Development Department

• Instructor interviewing, Writing syllabuses for new courses, Organizing instructors to design and expand courses, Financial accounting of the department, Preparing reports monthly and presenting them in the board of directors, Quality assurance of the classes and instructors, Managing staff regarding the consultancy and the way of working, etc

Tehran Institute of Technology, Vanak Delegacy

Tehran, Iran

June 2015 - February 2017

Director of Web and Development Department

• Instructor interviewing, Writing syllabuses for new courses, Organizing instructors to design and expand courses, Financial accounting of the department, Preparing reports monthly and presenting them in the board of directors, Quality assurance of the classes and instructors, Managing staff regarding the consultancy and the way of working, etc

Tehran Institute of Technology, Vanak Delegacy

Tehran, Iran

June 2014 - June 2015

Educational Specialist at Web and Development Department

• Giving consultation and roadmap to students, Managing classes and quality assurance, Resource acquirement for the classes, Keeping the contact with student and talk with them about their issues and problems, Preparing weekly reports on the sale and department's income, etc

Tehran Institute of Technology, Vanak Delegacy

Tehran, Iran

June 2013 - June 2014

Director of Organizational Education Department

• Keeping contact with educational departments of organizations, Organizing indoor and outdoor classes for the personnel, Consulting with other departments regarding technical details, Keeping contact with financial departments of organizations in order to receive the tuition fee of the classes, Preparing reports to be presented in the board of directors, etc

Tehran Institute of Technology, Vanak Delegacy

Tehran, Iran

January 2005 - April 2012

Instructor and Educational Specialist at Kids ICT Department

• Giving consultation to families about their kid's ICT education, Organizing classes for kids, Designing courses suitable for the kids about ICT concepts, Designing books or software for the children to learn ICT concepts more easily, Giving presentations at schools about ICT, Preparing reports and presenting them weekly to the director, etc

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

Afsaneh Sadeghnia

+31 (0) 615357770

Email: x.sadeghnia@gmail.com

Skype: x.sadeghnia

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/afsaneh-sadeghnia-1b32b5108 May 13, 2018 Page 3

COMPUTER SKILL

• Surfing and searching the Web and Internet (Expert)

- Microsoft Excel (Expert)
- Microsoft Word (Expert)
- Microsoft Power Point (Expert)
- Adobe Photoshop (Expert)
- Instagram, Facebook and other social networks (Expert)
- PHP (Intermediate)
- Java (Intermediate)

EDUCATION

• 2011 - 2013

Applied Scientific Comprehensive University

Tehran, Iran

Bachelor Degree in Information Technology Engineering - Web Department

GPA: 18.57

• 2004 - 2006

Applied Scientific Comprehensive University

Tehran, Iran

Associate Degree in Computer Software

GPA: 18.65

• 2001

Tolou 1 Highschool

Tehran, Iran

Highschool Diploma in Mathematics and Physics

GPA: 16.24